Heat. Heat.
Good evening ladies and gentlemen and
welcome to Credential Africa 2026
[music] Diamond and Emerald Club Awards
Gala. We are very happy to welcome all
of you in this special event. [music] We
hope everyone enjoyed the sunset
cocktails at the Pala rooftop. Now we
would like to invite all of you to be
seated at the [music] event as the event
will begin very shortly. Once again, if
you have entered the ballroom, ladies
and gentlemen, we'd like to welcome you
to please take your seats [music]
as our program will commence very
shortly. Thank you very much.
Once again, good evening, ladies and
gentlemen. Welcome to Credential Africa
2026 Diamond and Emerald Club Awards
Gala. We're very happy to welcome all of
you in this very, very special event. We
hope everyone enjoyed the sunset
cocktails at Pala Rooftop. And now we'd
like to invite everyone to please be
seated as the event will begin shortly.
Once again, if you have entered the
ballroom, please do take your seats as
our event or our program will commence
very shortly. Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
Credential Africa 2026 Diamond and
Emerald Club Awards Gala. Please have a
seat and enjoy the show.
Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat.
[music]
>> Heat. Heat. [music]
Heat.
[music]
When I look at you, I just feel like
you
want to
>> [music]
>> Heat.
Heat.
[music]
Oh yeah.
[music and singing]
[music]
Yeah. Yeah.
>> [cheering]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Where are you?
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Some more.
So more
[singing]
will
sorrow.
Baby,
so do you
No
rock.
So
war.
Oh my
god.
I
am
poch.
So
for you
for
the ring.
And the monkeying
[music]
>> [singing]
>> Someone
[singing and music]
[music]
I want [singing]
you
[singing]
[singing and music]
Yeah.
>> [singing]
[music]
>> Oh,
[singing]
[music]
heat, heat.
Heat.
[music]
Heat. [music]
Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat. [music]
Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
>> My [music]
[singing]
mother
see
[music]
[singing]
the sea.
>> [music]
>> Heat.
Heat. [music]
>> [music]
>> I know this
[music]
[singing]
Johnny
Jes.
[music]
[singing]
[music and singing]
Heat. Heat.
[music] Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat.
[music] Heat.
Oh,
[music]
I know
>> [music]
>> Good evening ladies and gentlemen,
distinguished guests and esteemed
dignitaries. Very warm welcome to each
and every one of you to Credential
Africa 2026
Diamond and Emerald Club Awards Gala and
welcome to the Apurva Campinsky here in
Bali, the island of the gods.
My name is Sophie Navita. Salamat malam
or maybe you already get to know it by
now means good evening and I will be
[music] your host for tonight throughout
our whole program.
First of all, why not give another big
round of applause for the opening
performance. Did you enjoy it?
That was a traditional Balines dance and
the chant and the dance symbolizes hope
for credential and everyone in this room
regardless of who you are to have a
prosperous and joyful and a year full of
health ahead. Ladies and gentlemen, what
you have just experienced in Bali um and
you have seen earlier in the highlight
videos has led us to this moment
tonight. It is truly a pleasure to see
all of you gathered here as we celebrate
this very very special occasion. So let
us start off tonight by getting to know
who is present in this room. And tonight
let's invite Mr. Ace Majija the chief
officer for commercial operations and
strategy to help us with this and also
extend a warm welcome to all of
dignitaries. Mr. Ace Maja the stage is
yours.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Why you guys sitting down? [music] Good
morning, potential.
>> Good morning, potential.
You guys look lovely tonight. You look
all beautiful
>> like the bunch of winners that you are.
>> First and foremost, welcome to your gala
dinner as we are celebrating you for
your performance last year. You guys did
great. The reason we here is because of
your performance. But before we start, I
do want to acknowledge a couple of
people and obviously starting with the
leadership team from Predential Africa,
Mukobi, our CEO who is here.
from the group team, our group
leadership team, our chief agency
officer, group chief agency officer
Pankash and chief
chief partnership distribution officer
for the group as well uh Patrick it's
PNP
and then most importantly I think uh the
CEOs of each country. So I'll ask one by
one as you stand as a CEO you stand with
your chief commercial officer as well as
your chief agency officer and then if
your team is here they must just make
loud noise to welcome you. Starting on
my list I've got Titi from Uganda.
[cheering]
Thank you, Tutti. Next up, I've got Fumi
from Nigeria.
[cheering]
H I'm going to skip this one. Next, I've
got Jane from Ghana. [cheering]
>> [cheering]
>> Next up, I've got Kaciza with his team.
Next up, I've got Canu with Etel.
>> [music]
>> And of course, we've got Gwen. She's
just made an entrance with Jane Tutu.
And then, of course, I'll be biased if I
don't announce my team, right? I've got
Vera, John, Jesus, Osui, and Roy.
If it wasn't for this team, we wouldn't
be here.
>> They've worked tirelessly to make it
happen. So, please give them a round of
applause again.
And obviously, Indonesia is our host
tonight. At least we are in their
country. And then we do have Mr. Hot
Palindugan. He's the VP for agency
business development from Predential
Indonesia.
Most importantly, we've got our
partners, uh, brokers from the various
markets. And I'll mention I've got
Josephine, uh, from Absa Bank, Uganda.
[cheering]
I've got Diana from Zenith Bank, Ghana.
Mr. Godfred Atafa from Fidelity Bank in
Ghana.
And then I've got Mr. Musand Kaba from
Zanako Zambia.
Chico Zimba from Indo Zambia Bank.
And then we do have uh brokers. We've
got our broker from Nigeria.
We also have our broker from Uganda
[music]
as well as in Zambia.
Fantastic. Now that this is done, I can
place it here.
[laughter]
Uh I always get a script which I tend
not to follow. So I go as the spirit
leads. But before we continue, I'd like
to invite Pankash on stage.
followed by [music] Patrick.
[music]
>> Do you have your dancing shoes on?
Do you have your dancing shoes on? I see
Patrick is ready.
So for me, I work for both channels,
agency and banker.
And I'll get the audience now to choose
which channel is the most exciting from
a dancing point of view.
This is the only time I get to give
instructions to Patrick and Pakash.
They would dance for us and we chose a
song for them just to bring the vibe and
the excitement to the room. I normally
bring the cos on stage. This time I
brought our visitors. Maybe I must bring
hot on stage too since you're a visitor.
You can come and join you. [laughter]
No worries. DJ, please give me that
song.
[music]
I am. I am. I am. [music]
>> [music and singing]
[singing]
>> Thank you, DJ. Give it up. Give it up.
>> We won more. Do you
>> But anyway, because I'm the judge,
>> they've both won.
>> They've done a fantastic job. And
because of that, they'll both say one
thing or two just for you guys to feel
their presence.
>> Good morning, potential.
>> Good morning.
>> How are you?
>> Fantastic. First of all, thanks to
Makobi and the entire African team for
having me here to join this amazing
event with all of you. And most
importantly, I want all of you to give a
big round of applause to yourself.
[cheering]
[applause]
and look at your right and look at your
left and give a big round of applause to
person sitting on your right and your
left.
Just
just imagine this if one of you
did not do what you did all of us
wouldn't have been here.
So that's the power that you bring to
credential. That's the power that you
bring to your own countries.
And on behalf of group agency and the
entire group office, I thank you for
your efforts. I congratulate you for
winning and being here. This night is
yours. Please have the maximum fun which
I think is about to come after we end
speaking over here. So once again, all
the best. Thank you for your passion.
Enjoy the evening.
>> I'm still out of breath.
I thought that would make me win, but
apparently not.
So, um yeah, I would acknowledge uh
Pankers, but I would really want to say
so Punkish and I join sometimes and we
get the honor to join these incentives.
one and and the reason why both I think
and speak for Bangs as well too that
we're always excited when Ace invites us
is because you guys show up. The way you
guys dress up is probably the best I've
seen across all our countries, guys.
Amazing. Seriously,
I think all these dresses probably has a
separate suitcases because it looks
awesome. Seriously, I am still out of
breath. Uh so um I just want to really
really say thank you to all to the bank
partners as well too to the brokers to
these as well too. Africa overall has
done amazing. It's really the results
the doubled growth that you have got
done again please congrat yourself
please please please it's so amazing
what you guys are doing as well too
and maybe then last so this is just a
personal thing when I visit a country
that I never been I always try to eat
the local food and I know we don't have
a lot of time left but my advice and you
can come find me as well too try if you
can eat it eat barbie and barbie means
pig and in Bali is very famous for it
because most of Indonesia is Muslim but
Bali is Hindu so they allowed to eat pig
and the most famous is Bobby Guling so
if you have time come fight me I will
tell you where to find it it's
ridiculous it's so good you will not
want to leave Bali anymore thank you I'm
out of breath thank you
>> thank you thank you thanks fantastic so
you do have time by the way I don't know
if you've heard the skies have been
closed kat and Dubai have been closed,
right, because of the war,
unfortunately, in Iran. So, you do have
time to try the Barbie if you're not
able to fly tomorrow. But with that
said, I do also want to really,
okay, don't go to your phones now and
check the news. But that's what's
happening right now. But without saying
much, well done for 2025. Patrick
touched on it briefly that we've done
doubledigit growth. Sh. Thank you. You
did very very well last year and you
started to doing well already in
January. And because it's the last day
of the month today, I'm sure the FAB
numbers are looking fantastic. I will
not ask you today, but tomorrow I'll
start asking you for the numbers. But I
do want you to enjoy yourselves tonight,
but also think beyond 2025 because this
is a new year and this is where you need
to pull up your socks. And most
importantly, the guys who are not here
tonight, they are also competing for the
same spots. As much as we have less
qualifiers this year because of other
things like persistence and so forth,
but the contribution of this room
has moved from 48% of AP to 65% of AP in
2025.
[applause]
And this is a group of just over 200
people out of 14,000 agents out of 1,500
bank people selling for us and the 200
of you have given us about 68% of our AP
and also NBP. So well done to
yourselves. You've done very very well
right but most importantly actually
Credential Africa across the group uh
there were different Northstar
championships that were ran last year.
Credential Africa had the most medals 74
and we won in our league because of the
stuff that we achieved last year. Most
importantly, two of our countries on the
bank assurance side won for NBP the
growth in NBP from the previous year. I
think that was Zambia and most
importantly the a NBP achieved across uh
bank assurance targets that was uh
credential Ghana. So well done to your
teams.
And if you remember last year, December,
we gave you a challenge. We gave you an
extra stretch in December to go beyond
your NVP. And we gave you that dollar
incentive. And of course, then Ghana
came out top cuz they exceeded that
target. [cheering]
And most importantly,
Dorothy and Gloria, they got recognition
for that achievement. So well done.
[cheering]
We do still have an incentive running
for the month of March if you've missed
Feb. So go back next week when you're
able to fly via Kata and Doha to get
those numbers. I won't spend too much
time, but I really want to congratulate
you, but for you to enjoy yourselves.
And I do hope tonight will prove to be
better than anything you've ever seen
before. And that will give you the
motivation that you continue in this
year to go over and beyond. And you
know, it's not just about meeting your
targets. Your targets are just the
threshold for qualification and then we
do the ranking and get those who are at
the top. So just because you think
you've qualified, it doesn't get you
there. Some of you have told me that
you've met your target for the year with
the January sales alone. But the guys
behind you are already pushing hard and
hard. So I really want you guys to enjoy
yourself. Dance away the night and then
there's an afterparty as well. Welcome
to the gala. Thank you.
[music]
>> Thank you very much Mr. Ace Mija. And
yes, I do agree with Mr. Patrick. Try
the Bobby Ghouling. It's true what they
say. It's really good. You have to give
it a try. Babiguling
and escalapa. Yeah. Young coconuts. The
um in their original casings. Okay. So,
don't get the one from from the bottle
once you're here in Bali. You need to
feel it straight from nature. As we
continue this wonderful evening, it is
our great pleasure to now extend a warm
welcome.
Please help me in welcoming the regional
CEO of Credential Africa who will be
delivering his keynote speech this
evening. Please give a warm round of
applause to Mr. Emmanuel Moi. I
[cheering and applause]
[music]
>> Good morning, Pencia.
>> Good morning, Pudential.
>> And how are you feeling today?
First of all, let me just say that is
you don't still get it. Tonight is a
night of celebration. Not to talk about
target in senses and all of those
things. Yeah, you got a chill on last.
We worked so hard last year and I think
it's time for us to enjoy. On that note,
good evening distinguished guest.
Um let me also recognize award winners.
Uh we have our partners here. I have my
colleagues here as well uh members from
the group the ar region um and then I
also have friends here. Welcome to this
special location and tonight we gather
here not to just do our gala dinner
but to celebrate excellence and that's
what is faced to meet. Now the kind of
excellence that defines who we are as
potential.
Every individual in this room has earned
their place to be here tonight.
You have qualified for this incentive
treat because of your outstanding
performance,
your discipline, your care
for our clients and your unwavering
commitment to protecting families and
building futures.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is our
seventh incentive trip and all over the
years we've celebrated in different
countries. I'm sure you aware of that
and each one has a memorable
way to remember it in its own way.
[clears throat]
But this year, I believe that you bear
with me that this year has been a truly
special incentive trip.
Now for the first time ladies and
gentlemen our achievers experienced not
one
but two incredible cities Jakarta and we
are here in Bali.
The dynamic energy of Jakarta
and the serene beauty of Bali.
From the vibrant PS of Indonesia capital
to the breathtaking landscape and rich
culture of this island paradise. This
journey reflects the scale of your
achievement.
It's expensive. It's inspiring and it's
unforgettable.
At Credentia, where our customers are
compass,
what we do matter deeply.
We don't simply sell policy, ladies and
gentlemen. We provide security. We
provide peace of mind and dignity to our
families in their most important
moments.
The results of these you have delivered
last year.
They represent lives protected, dreams
secured and future made more certain.
Excellence at this level calls for a
heart to serve client with integrity and
with purpose.
This is what you guys, all of us in this
room have been able to demonstrate last
year
as Africa CEO.
I could not be prouder of your
achievement.
You are not only top producers, you are
ambassadors of our values and proof of
what is possible when determination
meets opportunity.
Tonight we celebrate your success,
ladies and gentlemen. Over the past
days, we have enjoyed fellowship,
new experiences
and welld deserved relaxation.
I hope this trip energizes you, inspires
you as well and reminds you that
extraordinary performance leads to
extraordinary rewards.
2025 was a memorable year for all of us.
The end of it marked three years since
we launched our Africa strategy
and we have made significant progress in
terms of laying the fundamentals of this
business.
We have sharpened our footprints in
Africa
by divesting our interest in franophhone
countries and also acquiring 100% stake
in our Nigerian business.
We have in the course of that extended
our partnership with Zen Bank of Nigeria
and so right now Credential Africa we
are focusing on Anglo markets and that
in itself give us access to over 400
million people to sell to. We have a
powerful bank assurance partnerships
across all the markets we operate in.
We have over 100 branches over thousand
branches and more than 14,000 agents
across the continent focusing on
anglophone.
Additionally, we are able to expand
our banker relations with SCB to
catacord two new markets i.e. Kenya and
then Nigeria.
We have also seen a renewed focus on our
patience in terms of persistency.
We've also seen a renewed focus in terms
of our products. We've pivoted our
business a lot more into retail
and product mix health and protection.
And we are set ladies and gentlemen to
accelerate the business in Predential
Africa.
Ladies and gentlemen, through your hard
work, Credential Africa, as a set was
recognized at the group level
for emerging as a winner of the
Northstar Champions League. And you guys
need to be very proud of yourselves.
[applause]
If my facts are right, we're among the
three LBUs in Predential Africa to do
double digit. It's about 30 north not of
30 in the whole of Prodentia falling
behind Hong Kong, China and then India
and all of this ladies and gentlemen
wouldn't have been possible without your
hard work, dedication and commitment to
your careers and you deserve a round of
applause for this. [applause]
As we celebrate tonight,
I think I must also
speak about the road ahead.
This year, like I mentioned, is a year
of acceleration.
And in my mind,
acceleration means faster,
scaling higher,
thinking bigger.
It means transforming
strong performers into exceptional
performers. And if you didn't hear me,
transforming strong performers into
exceptional performers. That's what
acceleration means.
It means not only being satisfied with
yesterday's success for which we are
here today,
but using as a springboard for
tomorrow's breakthrough. That's what
acceleration means to me.
Now, it's important for me to know that
all of you gathered here are the leaders
for that acceleration.
If last year was about excellence,
this year is about elevation.
And so, I expect
and believe that each of you will align
with this vision.
And so scale up your performance,
deepening client relationships,
expand your network
and understand your relationship as well
and raise your standards even further.
The same determination that brought you
to Jakarta and Bali can take you even
greater heights. and I'm incredible
proud of what you guys have been able to
accomplish individually
and then as a group or team. But I'm
even more excited about what you guys
are capable of doing this year.
Once again, ladies and gentlemen, let me
take the opportunity to congratulate
each and every one of you.
Thank you very much for raising the bar.
Thank you for protecting lives and thank
you for being the driving force behind
this company.
To my great left and the CEOs,
the commercial heads,
thank you for leading the charge in your
respective businesses. I know I give you
guys a lot of pressure, but it's for
good reason.
I'm also aware that I have the bank
partners here as well as the brokers.
Thank you from my heart for supporting
this vision
and to the dedicated committee members
who made this event possible.
Thank you for your time. Thank you for
your effort and your contributions are
truly truly appreciated.
to my difficult colleagues from AR is
leading the team Vera another difficult
person and then representing from the
commercial function
your hard work is instrumental to our
continuous success of this company and
despite the fact that you give me a lot
of headaches I'm truly truly grateful to
you guys
now this is the most important aspect of
my speech
And guys, I would like to conclude this
speech by extending my heartfelt
appreciation to Prancash,
our group chief agency officer and
Patrick,
our group chief partnership distribution
officer.
I'm sure you will bear with me. The
reason why this is so special to me, if
for nothing at all, you saw the the
dancing that was displayed.
I've been with you guys for so long. I'm
not sure you guys have managed to get me
to dance and I'm not going to do so this
evening as well.
But most important more on the more
serious to thank them for their guidance
and support in driving our innovation in
Africa
in driving our growth in Africa and our
success in Africa.
Again most importantly I want to thank
them for spending time you know to show
presence here this evening.
Remember they were with us last year to
do the celebration
and this year again they are here. That
obviously show their commitment to the
African dream and guys I'm truly
grateful for that.
[applause]
I'm going to demand
from you, not the same way as AIDS did,
but my demand to you guys is that let's
continue to dream bigger.
Let's continue to achieve greater things
and therefore celebrate even more
milestone together. On that note, ladies
and gentlemen, enjoy the evening and
once again, congratulation to you guys.
>> [applause]
[music]
>> Thank you very much, Mr. Ai. Your
message tonight has [music] perfectly
framed the spirit that we all carry in
our hearts this this evening. Oo, I'm
sorry. This evening. [laughter]
All right, let's move on to our next
program. Ladies and gentlemen, at this
time, please do enjoy. But before that,
yeah, as uh people all over the world
do, you can fish out your cameras and
take pictures [music] of the local
Indonesian food that has been prepared
very carefully and with all their
hearts. It's a set menu prepared by the
talented chefs of the Apurva Campinsky
Bali. So let us mark this special
occasion with exceptional food, great
company and extraordinary celebration
and also nice pictures to bring home
with you so you can always have memories
of Bali and come back here with your
family next. And now we are delighted to
present one of the evening's most
anticipated highlights.
This is the awards ceremony.
We will begin with the Emerald Club
Award.
[music]
First of all, we'd like to welcome on
stage pres presenting the award tonight.
Let's give a round of applause to Mrs.
Vera Adomaku Nanteti,
regional director for strategic
partnerships and operations, credential
Africa.
[music]
>> [music]
>> All right. So, moving on. Please welcome
on stage the CEO of Credential Nigeria,
Mrs. Funio, and the CCO, Mrs. Toin
Adayor Ysu, to please present the
awards.
[music]
At this moment, we'd also like to invite
Mr. Emmanuel Oladi from Zenith Bank,
Nigeria to please join us on stage.
>> And to all the awardees, when your name
is called, please come up to the stage
to receive your award and join the first
group photo.
Afterwards, you'll be led by our [music]
ushers to the side stage. As you wait,
we will take the second group photo.
>> Ladies and gentlemen from Zenit Bank,
Nigeria for Nigeria Emerald Club Awards.
Congratulations to
>> Okay,
Oki.
>> [music]
>> She get
no like
she get
[music]
You see
[singing]
[music]
I
>> [music]
[music]
>> Congratulations
to Willie.
[music]
I pull up.
Highway
[music]
please. Welcome.
Good luck.
[music]
Daddy, you know we make you
>> [music]
>> make you pop champagne.
>> Ladies and gentlemen,
Abdul Fatani
>> and you're [music] giving me victory.
Everywhere I go, blessings follow.
>> Everything I do, [music] fame, follow,
kings are coming to my rising.
I'm going [music] higher by the grace of
God. Oh, oil on my hand.
>> Oil on my head.
>> Oil [music] on my hand.
>> Increase in my hands.
>> Increase in my hand.
>> Speed on my feet.
>> Speed [music] on my feet.
>> Everywhere I go.
>> [music]
>> Ladies and gentlemen, a story of [music]
sleep. Wake up.
Wake up.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Don't walk. Don't try
to die.
We don't mind [music] when I land softly
on floor. So far so good.
>> Congratulations. And now let's welcome
Chin Noabuchi eBay
[music]
[music] about time to take
>> [music]
>> Congratulations.
>> We're also happy for you.
Let's now welcome Omar Sle Umar.
[music]
I'm the only [music]
Yeah. Yeah.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Congratulations.
>> Next, let's welcome
[music]
body.
Back to your body.
I do it. [music]
Give me your body.
[music]
Congratulations.
>> Maybe we can see that happy dance once
more. Yeah. Next, let's welcome
[music]
Our body
breaks.
[music]
>> Thank you. Thank you. Maybe another
happy dance while you get to the side of
the stage. Let's now welcome Josephine
Olu.
[music]
Everybody that's for me that's for me.
Everybody that's [music] for meal.
[music]
>> Congratulations once again Josephine.
Let's now welcome. [music]
The other for that must you find
[music and singing]
I must try to make my name.
So when you [music] see my make
when [music]
[singing and music]
[music]
[singing]
Thank you very much.
And now congratulations to Leah Bosari.
[music]
Africa. [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Congratulations for you. Your hard work
paid off.
>> Thank you very much. Next, let's
welcome.
[music]
Everybody dance for me. Let's [music]
for everybody that's for
from [music] me.
Meow.
[music]
Give me.
>> [music]
>> Telma, what a beautiful spirit.
[music]
>> Yes, everybody smile.
Thank you. Congratulations once again.
[music]
And now let's welcome Chitty Chris Ioku.
Congratulations [music]
[music]
and thank you.
>> Next, let's welcome Marcos.
[music]
[music] 16 tracks.
Oh,
[music]
from me
from
[music]
16 tracks
from me
from
[music]
aha.
>> [music]
>> Wow. Congratulations, Marcos.
>> Thank you very much. And now we'd like
to welcome on stage Marta Onov.
Baby, please give [music] me tonight.
I'm going crazy.
Let me [music] let me
[music]
I'm going crazy tonight.
Wow. Congratulations, Marta. Thank you
very much. And now, last but not least,
let's welcome Adobe Morin.
Cuz
the way you [music]
like the way you [singing] make me want
[music]
baby.
Oh yeah. [music]
Oh baby.
Tonight I'm going crazy tonight.
[music]
>> Congratulations once again.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Congratulations awardies.
And please remain on stage for your
group photo.
Sh
[music] baby so
baby so fresh
baby so sweet
baby so
Sh
[music]
go
you
shake you
shake you [music] shake you shake shake
you
shake you shake you [music] shake you
>> All right everybody give your best smile
And then
please wait for another quick moment
as you wait for
the whole group photo
after this one award that we are going
to announce.
>> Yes. Everybody to the side of the stage
again.
>> Thank you so much for your patience.
Thank you. Thank you so much for your
patience.
>> And now we will carry on
to the next part of our awarding.
And now to our brokers
from Roman's insurance brokers.
Congratulations to Sund Rajan Balman.
We do bad things for good reasons. You
know I know you know and we do good
[music] things for reasons. You know I
know you know
[music]
we just want to have some fun tonight.
We are the happy people. We are [music]
the world.
[music]
>> Thank you very much. And Mr. Sunund
Rajan Balman please remain on stage. I'd
like to have the whole group to come
back up on the stage now. [music] And we
take the second group photo.
This is for Nigeria Emerald Club.
>> Congratulations Nigeria Emerald Club.
[music]
Do you know the truth? I'm not the
[music] only person. You are not too.
We are the happy people. We are the
world.
I
[music]
>> 5 4 3 2 1 cheese.
And then let's have one where you're
having this great big happy laugh.
Credential Africa.
[music]
>> All right. Thank you very much. Can we
give them a round of applause, please?
Ladies and gentlemen, you may [music]
return to your seats. Thank you very
much.
>> Congratulations.
[music]
Thank you to all our presenters. Yes,
you may return to your seats and enjoy
your dinner.
And we would like now to invite on stage
as we move on to the next award
presenting the Zambia Emerald Club
Award.
[music]
Miss Farah will now along with Mr.
Kacisa Kuenda CEO of Credential Zambia
and Mr. Blesset Muansa CCO of Credential
Zambia. Please do join us on stage.
[music]
>> At this moment, allow me to invite also
to the stage Mr. Mus Kabbe, head of
distribution for Zano Bank to please
also be with us here on stage. Thank
you, sir.
>> [music]
[music]
>> All right. Once again all the awardees
when your name is called please do come
up to stage you receive your award and
you join the first group photo. After
that kindly remain on the side of the
stage just as we've done before and
follow our ushers for more instructions.
We will be taking a second group photo
to represent your country, the Emerald
Club. Ladies and gentlemen, for the
Zambia Emerald Club awardees from Zanako
Bank, congratulations to God Shilaka.
[music]
Break [music] up
>> [music]
[music]
>> Wow.
Congratulations once again. Thank you
very much ladies and gentlemen. We will
now be welcoming Febala.
[music]
Hey
Nobody
[music]
>> [music]
>> Thank you very much. Congratulations
once again. And we will now welcome Leia
Muani.
[music]
I will never.
[music] Congratulations
[music]
>> once again. Thank you very much.
>> We will now invite Kelvin Zulu,
[singing] right?
[music]
>> [music]
>> AC [singing]
>> May I leave the room?
[music]
much. Let's now welcome Hope Mutal.
[music and singing]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Pull up.
[singing]
Look [music] nice.
Come on.
Thank you. Congratulations.
Thank you very much. We will now move on
to the next awardee. Let's welcome
Anthony.
[music]
[singing]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Congratulations.
Thank you very much, Anthony. Let's now
welcome Eric Muna
[music] like it's your birthday
[singing]
in the west
of my labor.
[music]
[singing]
No need to ask.
[music]
I just [music and singing] want to see
you goes
like [music]
[singing]
360.
>> Congratulations. Thank you. Let's now
welcome Buuya.
[music]
[music] I'm shooting my shots.
Can I get myself?
[music]
>> [singing]
>> looking
through.
>> Thank you very much. Congratulations
once again. And last but not least,
let's give a warm round of applause for
Vincent Musa.
>> 360. Okay. 360.
[music]
I am deep in my thoughts.
I'm shooting my shots.
[music] Can I get myself?
[music]
[singing]
All right, we will now have the group
photo. So, can we all please come back
on stage? Yes. Everybody. Everybody.
Yes. It's okay.
Everybody back on stage to do the first
group photo.
>> [music]
>> lady [singing]
[singing and music]
lady
happy
360s [music]
I'm shooting my shots
can I get myself that's
>> [music]
[music]
>> All right. Thank you very much. You may
return to the side of the stage. All
awardees and presenters from Zanako
Bank, please do come to the side of the
stage, please. On my side. Thank you
very much. Because we will now move on
to the next award. Thank you very much
all the awardees and the presenters from
Zana Cob Bank. Would you please join us
on the side of the stage?
>> All right. And now ladies and gentlemen,
for the next award, we'd like to invite
on stage, Miss Tiko Zimba from Bank
Assurance Manager, Indo Zambia. Please
come join us on stage.
360. Okay. 360.
[music]
And now, ladies and gentlemen, the
Zambia Emerald Club awardees for Indo
Zambia. Congratulations to
Joey Agnes Living.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Mr. skills on a mission they see on
television on the lowh
[music] on the lowh
on the low it on the lowh Yeah. On lowh
[music]
it on
it.
[music and singing]
>> Congratulations
Agnes Leinga. And now let's welcome
James Mui.
Coordinates
[music]
187.
Thank you very much. Congratulations.
Please remain on stage as we now have
your group photo. Yes, please. The group
photo for the Credential Zambia Emerald
Club awardees.
>> And then after this, it's the whole
group photo.
[singing and music]
>> All right,
let's not forget that beautiful,
beautiful smile that you brought all the
way from home here to Bali.
Congratulations.
[music]
And now let's have the second group
photo. Everybody will be coming up on
stage. This is for the Credential Zambia
Emerald Club Awards family group photo.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Oh my
Oh my n I
[music]
>> 5 4 3 2 1 smile.
>> Thank you.
>> Congratulations. And you may return to
your seats.
All awardes and honored presenters. You
may return to your seat except for Mrs.
Vera [music]
because we have to move on to Ghana now.
Thank you very much. So ladies and
gentlemen, if you're ready, because I
know I am, it's time for Ghana.
[music]
We'd like to invite on stage to present
the awards Mrs. Jane Mingle, the CEO of
Credential Ghana, and Mrs. Gloria Yamson
[music]
the CCO of Credential Ghana.
>> Yes, please. Good evening. Madame,
[music]
>> we will start with Zenith Bank Ghana.
So, kindly please join us on stage. Mrs.
Diana Hagen.
>> All right. Once again to all awardees,
when your name is called, please come up
to the stage to receive your award. And
then you will be taking the first group
photo. After that, you will be uh
escorted to the side of the stage by
your ushers while you wait for the next
group. And then we have another [music]
big group photo after this to repres
represent your country Emerald Club. All
right, let's start now. Ghana Emerald
Club awardees from Zenit Bank, Ghana.
Congratulations to Glattis Asar.
And you never [music and singing]
thought that I would be okay.
You lie. You lie to me. You [music] make
me what you dream. Coming back on your
knees. Oh no. [singing] Oh no.
[music]
See you go again. You won't get again.
Make you not disturb me [music] cuz I
know God mind you. Oh no.
It's too late. [music]
It's too late.
It's too late. [singing]
You lost a little [music] one.
[singing]
>> All right. Now, let's take a picture.
Congratulations, [music]
Gladice. You deserve this award.
[singing]
>> All right. Thank you. Congratulations.
>> Congratulations.
>> Thank you, Glattis. And also, Mrs.
Diana, you may Yes, please. [music]
Thank you very much. Join me on the side
of the stage as we proceed with the next
award. We will now continue with
Fidelity Bank Ghana. So, please kindly
join us on stage, [music] Mr. Godfred
Ayua as divisional director retail
banking of Fidelity Bank Ghana.
[music and singing]
[singing]
Everybody's up on stage ready to hand
over our awards. Let us start. Ghana
Emerald Club for Fidelity Bank.
Congratulations [music] to Emmanuel Oay
Sepha
R2.
Yeah.
[music]
Life is sweeter than but you for take it
[music] easy and make you know the rush
and blow your meter on. Just get your
hustle on then be fly.
Use your head. [music]
>> Congratulations.
>> Let's now invite Francisco Aensson.
Nobody
[music]
give you story but in the end [music]
they leave you lonely. So make your own
story.
One life
[music] I keep moving on. I'm a soldier.
I never lose the title. I'm a
[music] one.
I keep moving on. I'm a soldier. I never
lose the title.
>> [music]
>> Winners don't quit cuz quitters don't
win. God forgive us. Save us from sin.
Bless [music] us with success in a
couple of things and protect us.
>> Thank you. Congratulations once again.
>> Let's move on to the next awardy.
Congratulations for Isaac.
>> I spit raw naked. [music]
I think life is like whiskey from the
ghetto. Rich kid by the boot running
your game. When you dream, dream big
like the big [music] sis. M O money over
bridges. Mo money for bridges. M O
McDonald's Burger King and [music] spend
the rest of your life trying to lose
digits. Okay. Okay. The chill with a
drink like a drink. [music] Life is
short like weather.
[music]
>> Congratulations.
>> Now let's welcome Eugenia Nana Basau.
[music] I never lose the title. I'm a
holder. Yeah.
I keep moving on. I'm a soldier. I never
lose the title. [music] I'm a holder.
Yeah. I do my thing. Me do like them.
They rush. I be cool like I be hot like
I cross the line. I win. [music] I b
with
a new religion. [music]
So keep what you doing and don't watch
nobody.
>> Three, two, one. There you go.
Congratulations.
Let's now welcome Bridget Hansen
[music]
[singing]
on my way. Don't look [music] far away
when I
really like [music]
my way. Don't look far away. Don't you
never let go. Hold on to my thoughts.
[music] Hold on. Won't be my
[music] love.
[music]
>> Congratulations. Thank you very much.
Please join us on the side of the stage
while I announce now Bernarda
Beefy.
>> [music]
>> But I love you. One thing I show you.
Show you. Show you. On my [music] way to
you. On my way, baby.
I show you. Do you remember what I
[music] said? The [singing] way you love
me, the way you treat me, the way you do
me. Don't make I do this. Call me when
[music] you need me. I'm going to come
through with speed on my way.
Congratulations.
>> Yes. Thank you very much. Let's now
welcome Robert Ou.
[music]
Sky
[music and singing]
love.
[music]
>> Congratulations. Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen. Let's now welcome
Emmanuel and Oppo.
>> [singing and music]
>> I'm talking [music] to you in
particular.
[music and singing]
>> Congratulations. Thank you very much.
We will now welcome Janet Shuma.
Hold on to
>> Congratulations.
Now let's please welcome Unice Mam Adu
Jimi.
Oh [music] no.
[music]
I'm tell you the world.
Congratulations once again.
[music]
>> Thank you, Unice. We will now welcome
Burial Kafi.
>> [music]
>> Baby [music]
coming up. Coming up.
[music]
>> Congratulations. Thank you very much.
Let's welcome the second Ununice on this
team. Ununice Alan Ajo be [music]
[music and singing]
You coming up
Christian
Juliana
Rosina [music]
[music]
[music] Marie. Congratulations
and thank you very much.
[music]
Yes.
>> Oh no. [music]
[music]
congratulations. Thank you very much.
Let's now welcome Francis Quu Jamesi.
[music]
>> [music]
>> my
sex [music]
and my feelings.
I'll be your good boy. I'll be your
[music]
own.
>> Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
We will now welcome Augustine Coina
Miwa.
[music]
>> [music]
>> I love you.
[music]
Baby,
>> congratulations.
Let's now welcome Gigi.
[music]
>> [music]
>> in a hot [music]
in a hot. [music]
>> Thank you. Congratulations. [music]
>> Last but not least, let's now welcome
Cynthia Aimon Dark. Why [music]
me? Why me?
I want you.
[music]
All right, we take a picture and then
after that, Cynthia, please stay on
stage as your friends are going to come
back up on stage and you're going to do
the first group photo. Come on, guys.
Let's do our first group photo.
[music]
Angelina
[music] Mexico.
[music]
>> Okay, hang on. We have one more person
joining the other side and once he's
there we will take a picture. All right,
we're ready now. [music]
And yeah,
please stay on stage.
>> As now I'm going to invite back on
stage, Miss Diana
to please come back.
We will now do the credential Ghana
Emerald Club awards photog
[music]
smile.
Look at the camera.
>> Oh, I see some people doing it right.
smiling with their eyes. It's called
smiles.
[music]
>> Congratulations
all awardees for Credential Ghana
Emerald Club Awards.
>> Big happy family with so much success
tonight. You may return to your seats.
Thank you honored presenters for
presenting awards. You may also return
to your seats.
And now we move on to Uganda Emerald
Club Awarding.
[music]
Please join us on stage. Mr.
Avi the CEO of Credential Uganda and
Miss Felicia Kashi the CCO [music] of
Credential Uganda as well as Mrs.
Josephin Mutabuza principal office of
ABSA [music]
Bank.
Once again all awardees when your name
is called please come right up on stage
receive your award. you take the picture
and then join me on the side of the
stage as we wait for the second [music]
group to take their photo. And that's
how we go on from award to award. So if
everybody is ready, we will now start
the Uganda Emerald Club for Absa Bank.
Congratulations to
[music]
So quick.
Yeah.
[music and singing]
>> [music]
>> I'm dressed to kill.
[music]
[singing]
Congratulations. Thank you very much.
Let's now welcome
Yeah. [music]
[music]
[music and singing]
Yeah.
[music]
>> [music]
[singing and music]
>> Take a picture.
3 2 1. Congratulations. Thank you very
much. Now, let's welcome
[music]
>> [music]
>> Put yourself in my shoes, girl. If
you're not [music] mu, [singing]
[music]
>> thank you very much. Congratulations.
Heal down.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Baby,
[music]
come back.
>> [music]
>> take a picture
all smiles
>> and thank you. Congratulations once
again, ladies and gentlemen. And let's
now welcome Nan Lilian.
[music]
Baby
Thank you. Congratulations.
Last but not least for tonight from
Abster Bank, we have
Miriam Kag.
[music]
>> [singing]
>> Baby,
[singing]
[music and singing]
baby.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Thank you. Congratulations. And now,
please stay where you are. We will
invite your group back [music] on stage
and everybody is going to take the first
group photo. Thank you so much for being
so patient.
[music]
Okay, everybody, give your best smile.
You're going to want to keep this
picture with you. [music]
>> Nice photograph. All right. Thank you
very much. You may return to the side of
the stage along with Mrs. Josephine
Mutabuza.
You'll be waiting on the side of the
stage as I announce the next category
and then we will all take a country
photo. Thank you very much.
We will now move on to Uganda Emerald
Club for Equity Bank. Congratulations
Tarin Deura Kenneth
Production.
[music]
I'll be at [music] my door waiting for
my [singing] baby.
[music and singing]
>> All right, let's give that big smile.
Kenneth,
>> thank you very much. Kenneth, would you
join us to the side of the stage along
with Miss Felicia Kari? Yes, thank you
very much. Please join me on this side
of the stage. We will now proceed with
the next award. For this section, we'd
like to invite Mr. Paul Naga, chief
health officer, to please join us in
presenting this next award.
>> Thank you, Paul Nagi.
And so, ladies and gentlemen, if you're
ready, because I sure am ready. I cannot
wait for this next one. Now on to our
brokers.
Congratulations,
Padre Pio.
[music]
>> We have Stacy Margaret.
This is unusual. [music]
[music]
Congratulations. [music]
Thank you very much.
>> And now for the health awards.
Congratulations to Brett Oes.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Like a daily
like a
[music]
smiles tonight. Thank you very much.
Congratulations, Fred. I' I'd like to
invite now. Yes. This side. Thank you,
Margaret.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Rewards.
[music]
Congratulations. Thank you very much.
And last but not least, we have
[music]
Like
a daily like a daily. [music]
Good morning sunshine.
What a sunny day. What a sunny [music]
day. Oh yeah.
>> All right. After this we will first take
a picture for the health awards. So uh
Kato Sam Iwanga please stay where you
are and Fred and Margaret will now join
them
the health first and then after that
we will go on to the next group.
[music]
And now, oh, not yet. Okay. After this,
we will be taking another group photo
with Absa [music] Bank along with also
Mrs. Josephine Mutabuza and also Equity
Bank.
Kenneth will be coming back on stage
with Miss Felicia [music] Wari. Yes.
Come back. Yeah. The whole group photo.
Sir, please remain on stage. Yes, it's
another group photo.
>> Yes, ladies and gentlemen, this is the
next big group photo.
>> Congratulations, Credential Uganda
Emerald Club Awards.
One big happy family.
My heart is [music]
[music and singing]
for dinner.
[music]
Okay. Move to the right. Your right.
Maybe three steps.
>> Three steps. One, two, three.
>> Okay. Smile. Let's not forget the smile.
>> Okay. Thank you very much. You may
return to your seats. Once again, please
give a round of applause for Credential
Uganda Emerald Club. Thank you, Mrs.
Farah, yes, you may return to your seat.
Thank you so much for being such a
patient, beautiful woman,
being such a good sport,
just standing up and just presenting all
the awards.
Ladies and gentlemen, we still have
another round of awards to go, but I
know you are enjoying your dinner. Can I
just hear another round of applause for
those who have worked so hard with their
team and tonight they get to celebrate
it. I know this is all teamwork. It
totally is. It's not possible to achieve
this alone.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, I see
that you are probably now on to your
main course, set menu, meal of the
night. And so before we go on to our
next program, I'd like for you to relax
and enjoy. I have this very beautiful
uh group of musicians.
They're going to come up on stage and
they're it's an ensem. Yeah. So, make
sure tonight that you not just enjoy
your achievements and your victory as a
team with all your friends here who are
practically family, but also make sure
you take a lot of pictures.
You are going to want to take a lot of
pictures because tonight is an
unforgettable one. Especially because
this was the destination chosen this
year to be in Bali, the island of the
gods.
All right. And they as they are getting
ready,
please um conserve your energy because
we still have live band performing for
you. We also have the DJ coming up for
you. I see in Credential Africa,
everybody is a dancer.
Everybody can move so well. So maybe
after this I'm going to come over and
introduce myself to be your friend and
maybe you can teach me a few steps. Yes.
Yes.
All right. So we will be moving on to
the next part where uh we will be
enjoying this ensemble [music] or an
ensom if you may. That's how they
pronounce it in French I believe. Um, I
also like to thank you for being so
patient with all the photo sessions that
we have had to take. And most of all,
from the bottom of my heart, I'd like to
really, really thank you for being
patient with me. And I hope I have not
mispronounced
one name. I've been trying my best for
the past two days. And uh, Mrs. Farah
here was um my mentor. So yeah, I hope I
have pronounced it right. And if I
haven't, if you see me on the side of
the stage and you want to come tell me
how to pronounce your name right, I am
more than happy cuz I love to learn new
languages. Even though for now it's just
through a name, but I have learned so
much just in one night and one day
because we started rehearsing from
yesterday. So if everybody's ready, they
are ready. Ladies and gentlemen, please
give a round of applause for Moira and
Sam.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> Heat. Heat. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat.
Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat.
[music] Heat.
Heat. [music]
[music]
Heat.
Heat. Heat. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> I am
[music]
[music] Heat.
Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
>> Heat.
[music]
Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat.
Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. [music]
Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> that anymore.
island
[music]
feel.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat.
Heat.
[music]
Heat. [music]
Heat. Heat. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Seeing climbing.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Come here. [music]
Holy name.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat.
Heat. [music]
[music]
Heat.
Any
[music]
I'll give you
>> [music]
[music]
>> Thank you.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
>> Heat.
Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat.
Heat.
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat
up here.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat.
Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> More ensemble everybody.
Beautiful
kasi. That's how you say thank you in
Indonesian. And if you want to learn how
to say it in the local Balines language,
it's Matura.
Matura. It's quite a mouthful, [music]
but it's easy really. Thank you very
much, Moira Ensemble.
[music]
All right, so ladies and gentlemen, we
will now be proceeding to the next part
of our awarding gala. [music]
I hope you have had a very satisfying
dinner. We will have some more along the
way, but of course we have the after
party. So, please conserve your energy.
Eat more if you must [music] because you
need energy to dance the night away.
Okay, let's now continue with our
Diamond Club Awards.
[music]
presenting the awards here. Please
welcome on stage Mr. John Abbaka,
director of Agency Africa.
[music]
We're ready. It's time now for
Credential Pension Management Zambia
Diamond Club Award.
[music]
Joining us on stage, Mr. Kiwao,
the CEO of Credential Pension Management
Zambia and Mrs. Apple Zulu as head of
distribution.
>> Kindly reminding to all awardees once
your name is called come up on stage get
your award and kindly remain on the
tight stage afterward [music] as we
prepare to capture a group photo. All
right, ladies and gentlemen,
Credential Pension Management Zambia
Diamond Club Award. Congratulation goes
to
Chandabe.
[music]
Oh no. All my enemies [music] are
all [singing]
my [music] enemies are somebody.
All my enemies are
all my [music]
>> Let's take a picture.
3 2 1
>> Congratulations.
Thank you.
[music]
>> Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Ladies
and gentlemen, let's now welcome Teresa
Hudson.
[music and singing]
Once from the top [music]
[singing]
it [music]
fire light
[singing]
[music]
picture
>> Teresa Hudson. Congratulations
and thank you very much.
Next up [music]
moving on. Congratulations Sarah Nandu.
[music]
>> [music]
>> All right, take a
Sarah, this is your night. Smile.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Let's now congratulate
Dina Perry.
[music]
>> [music]
>> I love your
number.
[music]
We're going to take a picture now with
Dina.
>> Oh, I bet you're going to dance the
night away tonight, Dino, at the after
party. Congratulations. Thank you very
much. Now, let's welcome Joanna Kaboom.
[music]
>> [music]
>> I want a manaly
[music]
>> [music]
>> Congratulations. Thank you very
I got
my
[music]
beauty in my beauty.
All right, congratulations. Thank you
very much.
>> And now, last but not least, Anoa
Changa.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Anawa Changa will now take a picture and
after this please remain on stage as I
call up the rest of the group to have a
group photo.
Can you please remain on stage madam?
Thank you very much and yes, let's have
the whole family back up on stage. Thank
you for your patience. We will now take
the credential
pension management. Credential Zambia
pension management.
And here we are. Credential pension
management. Zambia Diamond Club group
photo.
Remember
my one and only. Together we shine
[music]
forever. Together
we'll
dance.
>> Thank you very much [music] to all the
awardees. Thank you for our
distinguished presenters. You may return
to your seat.
[music]
together.
>> We will now move on to present Kenya
Diamond Club Award.
[music]
>> Kindly, please join us on stage to
present the awards. Mrs. Gwen Kinesisu,
CEO, Credential Kenya, and Mrs. Jenutu,
CAO, Credential Kenya.
>> [music]
>> Yes, do join us on stage. And to all the
awardees once again, once your name is
called, you can straight away rush to
the stage, receive your award, [music]
take a picture,
and then follow the instructions of our
ushers as we take pictures of other
awardees while you [music] wait for the
group picture to be taken. Thank you
very much.
All right, let's start.
Kenya Diamond Club Award.
Congratulations to
Agata Wira.
You [music] got me.
You got me. You got me. You got me.
[music]
That's why I never falling down.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
[music and singing]
>> smile. Yes. Beautiful.
>> Thank you very much. Congratulations.
Moving on now. Still on the credential
Kenya Diamond Club award. Let's welcome
Abigail.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Come see papa.
Come see papa. [music]
Papa
[music and singing]
way papa.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
[music]
Thank you. Next, please welcome Edith.
[singing]
>> [music]
[music and singing]
>> Come see papa sing
[music]
it go. Take a picture.
>> [music]
>> Great. Congratulations. Thank you very
much, Eden.
>> Congratulations. Next to Grace Muryuki.
[music and singing]
[music]
Congratulations. [music]
We're taking a picture now.
[music]
>> Congratulations. Thank you very much,
Grace. [music]
>> Let's now welcome Alexangi.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hallelujah.
[music]
Hallelujah.
[singing]
>> [music]
>> Thank you and congratulations, Alex.
Next, let's welcome Steve.
[music]
Baby.
Oh. [music] Oh. Sh.
[music]
Congratulations, Steve.
Is Steve the team favorite? [laughter]
>> Looks like it. Yeah.
>> Thank you very much. Congratulations,
Steve.
Next, let's congratulate Rose Miso.
[music]
Oh [music] baby.
Oh [music]
sh
[music]
original. [music]
O original style. Yeah.
[music]
[singing]
>> Yes. Congratulations. Thank you once
again. Now, let's welcome Josephine
Gucci.
[music]
Mama King.
Oh
baby oh
my [music]
go
[music]
[music] from the house.
>> [music]
>> Got you. [music]
[singing]
Congratulations.
Let's now welcome Patrick M.
[music]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, baby. Oh go.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Take a picture now is Patrick Aber.
Thank you. Congratulations, Patrick.
Next, let's welcome Bernard Oare.
[music]
>> [music]
[singing]
>> Come see [music] papa.
Come see papa sing [music]
papa
[singing]
[music]
papa.
Congratulations Bernard Obo.
>> Congratulations
and
thank you for being [singing] a very
good team player. You're here tonight.
Next, let's welcome Gladis Ki.
[music]
>> [music]
>> I'm going to figure
[music]
things
like
>> [music]
[music]
>> Clap clap
things.
>> [music]
>> Congratulations and thank you Glattis.
Next, let's welcome the other Glatties
they have on this team, Glattis White.
[music]
Shake, shake, shake your mama. Shake
well before you [music] come shake. Come
shake shake that thing [music]
that
shake that thing.
[music]
Congratulations goddess.
[music] Right.
Thank you very much and once again
congratulations.
Next we have Grace.
[music]
[music and singing]
I want to show you all. Show you. Show
you. [music]
I'm finished. I want to show you. Show
you. Show you. [music]
[music]
[singing]
This is Grace Mongari Guter.
Congratulations.
Let's now welcome
Patros and Jerry.
[music]
[singing]
I want to show you. [music] Show you.
Show you.
I want to show you. Show you. Show you.
I will finish you with my love.
[music]
[singing] Right. [music]
Congratulations. Thank you very much. We
will now welcome Amy Muri.
[music]
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> I want to show you.
[music] Show you.
I want to show you. Show you. Show you.
[music]
Finish.
Right. Congratulations and thank you Amy
Kiro Muri.
And now let's welcome Grace Gooie.
Sh. [music]
[music]
My
heart tonight.
[music]
[singing]
>> Thank you very much and congratulations
once again for Grace.
Next, let's welcome Stephie Muanzia.
[music]
Oh
my
go.
[music]
>> Thank you. Congratulations, Stephie.
Let's now welcome
Daniel Outu.
>> [music]
>> Oh no.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Thank you, Daniel. [music]
Congratulations.
>> Let's now welcome Charlene Kimara.
>> [music]
>> Oh no.
I'm knocking down.
[music]
Woo!
And Charlene, if you would please remain
on stage, I will have the rest of the
group come back up and we are going to
take a group picture.
All of you, Credential Kenya Diamond
Club Awardy.
figure
[music]
that
things
[music]
that
itap [music]
Clap. Round of applause.
>> Take a picture. Five. Four.
Three. Two.
One.
Kenya Diamond Club awardy. Thank you so
much. We'd like to congratulate all
awardies. Thank you for our presenters,
Mrs. Gwen Kinu and Miss Janeu.
You may return to your seat.
Let's now move on.
Next in line is Nigeria.
>> [music]
>> presenting the award. Please welcome on
stage Mrs. Funme Almo, CEO of Credential
Nigeria and Mr. Quaberna Yenki, CEO, CEO
of Credential Nigeria.
Please welcome them on stage.
>> Mrs. Funi Omo,
there we go. And Mr.
All right, let's go. And for Nigeria
>> for the credential Nigeria Diamond Club
award. Congratulations to Bedrack Eduga.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Big moves only.
[music]
Big flex only.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Congratulations
and thank you very much.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Next, let's welcome
tou Paulo.
[music]
>> [music]
>> is coming
[music]
be flex. [music]
>> Congratulations, Paul.
Let's now welcome
Zum.
[music]
Because I swear God [music]
bless.
>> [music]
>> Congratulations. Thank you very much.
And now let's welcome.
[music] We making money rush like
that
[music]
baby show
[singing]
[music]
because I swear.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Thank you and congratulations.
Last but not least, we have Joy Chor.
>> [music]
>> Hallelujah.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Yes. Thank you. Congratulations. Please
remain where you are. I'm going to get
the rest of the group to come up and we
will take a group picture for Credential
Nigeria Diamond Club.
[music]
>> [music]
>> I don't know. I [singing] can't picture
this without you, my life. [music]
>> Okay, let's give a great big smile for
this [music] group photo.
Thank you very much. Congratulations
once again to all awardees.
Thank you [music] also to Mrs. Funmi Omo
and Mr.
Thank you. You may return to your seats.
>> We will now move on to the next [music]
category.
It is now time for Credential Zambia
Diamond Club Award.
I'd like to invite Mr. Kachuza Kuenda,
CEO of Credential Zambia and Mr. Blessed
Wansa,
CCO of Credential Zambia. Please join
us.
>> All right, let's start.
Credential Africa 2022 Diamond and
Emerald Cup Awards Gala Tonight. This
time it's for Zambia.
Let's congratulate
Shula Mena.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Whatever
my voice,
[music]
thank you and congratulations.
Next, let's welcome
Mercy Shambo.
[music]
Hey [music] jealous.
>> [music]
[music]
>> congratulations once again. Thank you
very much. Now let's welcome Monica
Malala Malonga.
[music]
>> [music]
>> I'm going
I'm going [music]
nobody [music] nobody
nobody nobody
>> [music]
>> Thank you and congratulations once
again, Monica. Next up, we have Gford
Mindu.
[music]
>> [music]
>> My goal
[music]
is
when I
[music]
>> congratulations.
>> All right. Yes. Thank you.
Thank you. Please join us at the side of
the stage. Yeah. Wow. Yeah. You guys are
having a party back there.
>> Next up, let's congratulate Eric Ready
Hapenza.
[music]
>> [music]
>> No gold.
[music]
[singing]
Congratulations. Thank you very much,
Eric.
>> Let's welcome Elliot Monga.
[music]
My phone nozzle.
[music and singing]
[music]
Thank you very much. Congratulations.
>> Congratulations. Now, let's welcome
Miriam
[music]
[singing]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Thank you and congratulations
Miam.
Let's now welcome
[music]
you now.
>> [music]
>> Congratulations. Thank you very much.
Let's now welcome Peter and Coley.
[music]
You know,
hey Hey,
>> let me take him back one more [music]
time. Hey
[music]
>> [music]
>> Thank you. Congratulations, Peter. Next,
we have Hope Simal.
[music]
Got [singing] it all. Yeah.
[music and singing]
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Congratulations hope let's [music]
welcome Jeff Mumbi
[music]
finger
My feelings
when I see you. [music]
[music]
[singing]
Congratulations. Thank you very much.
Let's now congratulate
Bango.
[music]
[singing]
Congratulations. Thank you very much.
>> Let's welcome Chilei.
[music]
Everything I know was this year.
>> High I go.
>> High I go. [music]
>> I get big I get.
>> It's my turn.
>> [music]
>> This year I go I go
>> it's my time.
[music]
>> Congratulations.
Please help me welcome Harriet Dawa.
[music]
[singing]
This year I study prosperity.
[music]
Lift your hands and say amen.
Amen. [music]
My hands are blessed. Amen.
Amen. [singing]
No strange.
[music]
>> Thank you. Congratulations, Harriet.
Let's now welcome Catherine Green Pitt.
[music]
Amen.
Say, "Amen." [music]
Amen. Empty body.
[music]
No struggle. No. No. No. [music]
This year. This year. This year.
>> Congratulations, Catherine.
>> Let's now welcome
>> Mercy.
I [music]
>> big I get big I get
>> it's my turn
I
[music and singing]
get it's my turn [music]
you [singing]
my this year this year [music]
blessing
>> [music]
>> Thank you. Congratulations.
Let's now welcome on stage innocent.
Beat.
[music]
>> Congratulations.
>> Let's now welcome Oscar for
[music]
[singing]
Congratulations Oscar.
>> [music]
>> Right. Thank you. Congratulations. Now,
please help me welcome Patricia.
[screaming]
[music]
>> [music]
>> We shall be back.
[singing] We are now back.
[music]
>> [singing]
>> Congratulations, Patricia.
>> Thank you very much.
Let's now welcome on stage Anderson
Innocent Musco.
[music]
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Congratulations Anderson.
Let's invite on stage Nandipulu.
[music]
You better see me too. You better see me
too. You better see [music] me too. Oh,
[music]
>> Congratulations. Thank you very much.
Next up, we have
[music]
Everybody,
[music and singing]
[music]
Congratulations.
Mercy.
>> And last but not least, we have Chrisin
Anthony Tempo.
In the meime.
[music]
>> All right. So, everyone, can you please
stand on stage? And everyone will now
come up on stage. We take the group
picture.
>> Yes. Everybody. Everybody. We take the
group picture.
>> [music]
[music]
>> We're going to go a little bit to your
left
>> so we can get everybody in the frame.
[music and singing]
>> Okay, look at the camera.
>> 5 4 3 2 1 smile. Yes. Thank you.
Congratulations once again.
>> Credential Zambia Emerald Club.
All right,
>> congratulations awardees. Thank you Mr.
Kajisa Quinn and Mr. Betena. You may
return to your seats.
And now
the credential Ghana Diamond Club Award.
And to present the award, Mrs. Jane
Mangal, CEO, Credential Ghana, and Mrs.
Dorothy Chitty, CAOO, Credential Ghana,
please join us on stage. Thank you.
>> As always, awardees, once your name is
called out, please come up to the stage
to receive your award, [music]
take a picture, and wait for further
instructions from our ushers. Let's get
ready for this one, ladies and
gentlemen.
Credential Ghana Diamond Club Award.
Congratulations.
First one up on stage goes to Alyn Sinam
Kachi
baby.
Okay.
[music]
I'm underneath a sexy face. [music]
I'm a pretty [music]
fresh
one.
>> Thank you very much. Next we have Romeo
[music]
like fresh.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much. Next, let's welcome
Patrick Aedu.
>> Fresh [music]
lollipop. Fresh girl lollipop. A fresh
boy
monkey. [music]
[music]
Congratulations.
Thank you very much, Patrick. Now it's
Whose turn is it
[music]
a girl with a sexy face. The boy down
[music] here with a pretty face.
[music]
>> Hi, congratulations.
And [music] thank you very much.
>> Next up, we have
Arthur.
[music]
>> We used to sneak up in them big waves.
You used to want to pull [music] me this
week, that sweet, this week, that sweet.
You just wanted to be in my arms. Yeah.
She said tonight, tonight, tonight I
don't [music] want to see no daylights
now. We don't want to see no daylights
now. Everything is too okay right now.
[music]
Congratulations.
Arthur.
>> Let's welcome now Mercy Anan. [music]
Po [music]
got to go to Po [music]
at [music] the movies
popcorn smelling smoothies.
>> Congratulations Mercy Anna.
>> Let's now welcome Loretta Ado Asarare.
That's why is [music] the king's bed
not thrown or roof just a shadow shed.
[music]
Break by brick we build from bed
under [music] the street [singing]
lights we cover our name.
[music]
There was no prolonged
fight.
We chase the dark through endless
nights.
[music]
>> Congratulations, Loretta. [music]
>> Next up, we have
[music]
>> Congratulations
I'm staying real everyone
will hear.
[music]
>> Congratulations. Thank you.
>> Next up, let's welcome Deborah Bazi Ai
Ai.
>> [music]
>> Once again, Deborah Bazi Hamble.
[music]
Thank you. Congratulations, Deborah.
>> Let's now welcome [music] Georgina
Hughes.
[music]
[singing]
minimum.
He is changing my life. He's giving me
[music] victory.
When I'm in trouble, you come and set me
free. [music] So I will give you thanks
and praise. I serve my living God. I
serve a mighty [music] God. Come on,
help me [singing] save. My life is
giving me victory.
When I'm in trouble, you come and set me
free.
So you
>> Thank you. Congratulations, [music]
Georgina.
>> Yes. Next up, let's welcome Josiah.
[music]
[singing]
>> [music]
>> So all my saints and praise
[music]
changing my life. He's giving me
victory.
>> Right.
[music]
>> Thank you, Josiah.
Next up, we have Abraham Ou.
I serve a living [music] God. I serve a
mighty God.
>> Come on, help me see my life. He's
giving me victory. Give [music] me the
victory.
When I'm in trouble, you come and set me
free.
>> Set me [music] free.
>> So, you set
[music]
in my life is giving me victory.
>> Victory.
When I'm [music] in trouble, you come
and set me free.
>> So I will give you [music] that example.
>> Congratulations, Abraham.
Let's welcome Priscilla Aua.
[music]
Right.
He is taking my life is giving me
victory. [music]
When I'm in trouble, he's going to set
me free.
You know, I believe you [music]
praise.
[music]
>> Yes, Priscilla. Beautiful.
Congratulations.
Let's now welcome Fatty Adote.
>> [music]
>> You make me want to dream. Coming back
on your knees. Oh no. Oh
[music and singing] no.
See you go again. You won't get again.
[music] Make you not disturb me cuz I
know God [singing] mind you. Oh no.
It's too late. [music]
It's too late.
It's too [music] late.
It's too late. [music]
You lost a [singing] little one.
[music]
[singing]
It's too late. [music]
>> Congratulations, Fati.
>> Next, we have Duke.
[music]
>> Oh, I love his tuxedo.
Beautiful. [music]
[music]
s.
>> Thank you and congratulations Duke. Next
up we have Sylvia Jackie Tu
[music]
make you not disturb me cuz
[singing and music] I don't mind you. Oh
no
it's too late.
It's too late. [music and singing]
It's too late.
[music]
>> [singing]
>> You know [music] those my
shooia.
[music]
[singing]
>> Next we have Ivy Salazi Kiss.
My life
[music]
used to [music]
get silence.
Congratulations. Thank you very much.
Next up, we have Safo Prince
[music]
and the right one open.
[music and singing]
I know they try to be one of them.
[music]
I chase my cities. I
tread carefully.
Some people are talking measulations
[music]
prince.
>> Let's welcome Emmanuel.
down.
Left eye clos.
[music]
[singing]
>> Congratulations, Emmanuel.
Let's welcome Asana Salipu.
[singing]
Down.
>> Congratulations, Asana.
Let's welcome Marta Aman.
[music]
Mama, where are you going? Mama,
where you going? [music] Mama,
[music]
baby, I'm in
[music and singing]
baby.
>> [music and singing]
>> Congratulations Marta. Let's welcome
Michael Odante Mills. [music]
[music]
I am down. Oh yeah.
[music and singing]
[music]
[singing]
>> Congratulations. Thank you, Michael.
>> Let's now welcome Emerald Regina Dodu.
I'm say my [music]
baby
drop Baby,
[music]
baby,
baby, [music and singing]
baby.
[music and singing]
>> Congratulations, Emerald.
Let's welcome Yayra Podo.
I
want
I [music]
Congratulations
Yaya photo.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, let's give it up
for Gideon A.
>> It's a beautiful brand new day.
[music]
Go reply Tuesday
[music] a
I'm